the useful feature with that word is the
ability to use templates to create your
documents to access the templates within
word you would first need to click on
fail then you and rather than select a
blank document option you will then be
able to select from a range of templates
that have already been designed and
created to be used for a variety of
tasks such as business purposes cards
Flyers letters educational documents
resumes and cover letters and holidays
as you scroll down the list of templates
and you find one that you like you would
simply click on the template that you
wish to use it will then give you a
preview of the template and from that
preview you would going to say that if
you like the template you would simply
click create and what is it once it has
been created in the word document you
would simply populate it with your own
information as you can see all of the
formatting has been applied it has some
color banding to the side different font
sizes different font styles
somewhere to place an email address and
the structure and layout have already
been pre formatted for you